剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
这不是你们的岛
This is not your island.
这是我们的岛
This is our island.
他们攻击我们  分裂我们   绑架我们  谋杀我们
They've attacked us,sabotaged us,abducted us,murdered us.
我们都知道这个岛上还有其他人
We're not the only people on this island,and we all know it!
第一晚他们来  抓走了三个人
They came the first night,took three of us,
第二次  又抓走了九个人
then they came back and took nine more.
他们聪明而且凶残
They're smart,and they're animals.
你们跟我们走
You're coming with us.
When you're alone
and life is making you lonely
You can always go…
Downtown…
When you've go worries all the noise and the hurry
seems to help I know…
Downtown…
Just listen to the music of the traffic in the city
Linger on the sidewalk where the neon signs are pretty
How can you lose
The lights are much brighter there
You can forget all your troubles
Forget all your cares
so go downtown
Things will be great when you're downtown…
No finer place for sure… downtown…
我把松饼烤焦了....还有我的手...
I burnt my hand...and my muffins.
还没修好吗?
Still hasn't fixed your plumbing yet?
工作正在进行中
It's a work in progress.
这根本不是文学作品  只是部闲书
It's not even literature. It's popcorn.
为什么不是  Adam?
And why isn't it literature, Adam?
我很想知道
I'm dying to know.
里面没有比喻
There's no metaphor.
只有些数字和宗教传闻
It's by the numbers,religious hokum-pokum.
-没有比喻?     -这是科学小说
-No metaphor?  -It's science fiction.
现在我知道为什么Ben没有来
Now I know why Ben isn't here.
什么?
Excuse me?
我知道应该由主人选书  但是说实话  Juliet 他根本不会浪费时间看这本书
I know the host picks the book,but seriously,
Julie,he wouldn't read this in the damned bathroom.
Adam  我就是主人  我选了这本书 并且这本是我最喜欢的
Well,Adam,I am the host,and i do pick the book,and this,is my favorite book,
我真的相当"内疚"你不喜欢它
so I am absolutely thrilled that you can't stand it.
我很愚蠢  居然选择了Ben不会喜欢的东西
Silly me for sinking so low as to select something that Ben wouldn't like.
所以我想 大家还是可以自由的选择...
Here I am,thinking that free will still actually exists on...
去门口
In the doorway,get in the door way.
Goodwin
看到飞机尾部落在哪里了吗?
You see where the tail landed?
看到了  应该在海里
Yeah,probably in the water.
跑过去  一小时就能到海滩
You run,you can make that shore in 1 hour.
Ethan  去机身那里
Ethan,get up there to that fuselage.
应该会有幸存者  你就假装是他们的一员
There may actually be survivors,and you're one of them.
一个乘客  装得惊慌点
A passenger,you're in shock.
他们问起的话就编个故事
Come up with an adequate story if they ask.
没问你就不要说
Stay quiet if they don't.
边听边学  别搞砸了
Listen. Learn. Don't get involved.
三天内我要拿到乘客名单
I want list in three days.
快去
Go.
我想我已经退出图书俱乐部了
So I guess I'm out of the book club.
迷失
第三季 第一集
Kate
你能听见我吗?
Can you hear me?!
Kate
该起床了  Kate
Rise and shine,Kate.
我在哪里?
Where am I?
你认为我会回答你这个问题吗?
You don't really think I'm going to answer that,do you?
Sawyer和Jack在哪里?
Where are Sawyer and Jack?
我给你个建议
I'll tell you what.
洗一个舒服的热水澡
Why don't you just take a nice hot shower?
让你自己清醒一点
Wake yourself up.
洗去疲惫  轻松一下
Wash the day off you and...start fresh.
-这里有很好的毛巾 香波 香皂    -我才不在你面前洗澡
-It's a nice clean towel,shampoo,soap...  -I'm not showering in front of you.
Kate...
你不是我喜欢的类型
You're not my type.
我们在哪里?
Where are we?
你们到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?
你不和我说话吗?
You ain't gonna talk to me?
怎么  你有更重要的事要做?
What,you got more important things to do?
*警告*
Warning
如果是我  我就不那样做
I wouldn't do that.
如果我想听你的意见我会问你的
I want your advice, I'll ask for it.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
知道厉害了吧
Told you.
停下来
Stop that.
你好  Jack
Hi,Jack.
我是Juliet
I'm Juliet.
你好
Hi.
-我是Jack Shephard
-I'm Jack Shephard.
-我来这里...       -你的律师呢?
-I'm here for the...  -Where's your lawyer?
你今天很漂亮
You look pretty.
你的律师呢?
Where's your lawyer?
我炒他鱿鱼了
I fired him.
Sarah...
我很抱歉让我们到了这个地步
I'm sorry,for...for pushing us to this place.
我...
I...
我知道我...
I know that I...
不好意思  抱歉
Excuse me,I'm sorry.
喂?
Yeah?
还没有好
No,not yet.
他刚刚才到
He just got here.
等我出去的时候再给你打电话
I'll call you when I get out.
-Jack 我尽量说的简单点    -他叫什么名字?
-Jack,I'm gonna say this as simply as I can.  -What's his name?
-别这样 Jack    -我不会停下来
-Jack,stop it.  -i'm not gonna stop it
如果你不告诉我我会一直问下去
I'm gonna keep asking you that until you tell me.
-我没有问你关于你的...         -告诉我他叫什么名字
-I don't ask you what you're doing...  -Just tell me what his name is.
我想知道他是谁
I wanna know,who he is.
听着  你什么都可以拿走 车子  房子
Look,you can have everything,the cars,the house.
我不在乎  我只是...
I don't care. I just...
我只是想知道和我老婆...
I just wanna know,the name of the man...
在一起的男人叫什么名字
that is with my wife.
Jack?
可以听到我说话吗?
Can you hear me in there?
那表示"可以"吗?
Is that a "yes"?
我的朋友在哪里?
Where are my friends?
先从桌子上下来
Come down from the table first.
你想我下来就过来把我弄下来
You want me to come down,come in here and get me down.
-如果你想谈谈  我很高兴...   -告诉我我的朋友在哪里
-If you wanna talk,I'm happy...  -Tell me where my friends are!
我会的...如果你放开铁链的话
I will...if you let go of the chain.
你认为我傻吗?
You think I'm stupid?
我不认为你傻  Jack
I don't think you're stupid,Jack.
我认为你很顽固
I think you're stubborn.
我的衣服在哪里?
Where are my clothes?!
(穿上这些)
来吧  Kate
Come on,Kate.
他已经在等了
He's waiting.
对不起  我必须让你带上手铐
Sorry,I'm going to have to ask you to put those on,Kate.
如果我不呢?
And if I don't?
那你就喝不到咖啡
Then you don't get any coffee.
再紧一点
A little tighter.
可以吗?
Please?
你对Sawyer和Jack干了什么?
What did you do with Sawyer and Jack?
为什么是Sawyer?
Now,why Sawyer?
什么为什么?
Why Sawyer what?
为什么Sawyer是你第一个问起的人... "你对Sawyer和Jack干了什么"
He's the first one you asked about "what did you do with Sawyer and Jack?"
你不了解我
You don't know me.
当然我不了解你
Of course I don't.
我想要回我的衣服
I want my clothes back.
我们把你的衣服烧了
We burned them.
你为什么把我带到这里?
Why did you bring me here?
你为什么让我穿这身衣服?
Why did you make me put on this dress?
你为什么让我吃早餐?
Why are you feeding me breakfast?
我带你来看海让你觉得舒服点
I brought you here so you'd look out at the water and feel comforted.
因为你的朋友也在看这片海
Comforted that your friends were looking out at the same ocean.
我让你穿这身衣服让你看起来像位女士
I gave you the dress so you'd feel like a lady,
我让你用叉子吃早餐让你感受到现代文明
and I wanted you to eat your food with a real live fork and feel civilized.
我做这些事情让你心情愉快点
I did all those things so that you'd have something nice to hold on to.
因为  Kate...
Because,Kate...
接下来的两个星期会很不愉快
the next two weeks are going to be very unpleasant.
你好
Yeah, hi.
我在火车上遇到一个女人...Sarah
I met a woman on the train,Sarah,and,
我捡到了她的手机 但我不知道她姓什么
she dropped her cell phone,and I don't even know her last name,
但是我看到你的电话号码在她的手机里 所以我想...
but your number was in her phone,so I was just wondering...
对不起  对不起  算了
I'm sorry,I'm sorry.Forget it.
等一下  爸爸
Just give me a minute,dad.
我不是让你等一下吗?
I asked you to give me a minute here.
这是什么?
What's this?
为什么你打这些Sarah手机上的电话?
Why are you dialing all the numbers on Sarah's cell phone?
因为他们当中有一个是和她在一起的男人
Because one of them is him.
你不能这样做 Jack
You gotta stop this,Jack.
已经结束了
It's over.
除非我知道他的名字  他在哪里工作  他住在哪里
Not until I know his name,where he works,where he lives.
他们在哪里第一次接吻
When they first kissed.
我想知道他是一个怎么样的人
I wanna know what it is about him.
爸爸  为什么Sarah会给你打电话?
Why is Sarah calling you,dad?
我觉得你应该就此罢手了
I think it's time that you let this go.
她为什么会给你打电话?
Why is she calling you?
-因为她担心你 - 爸爸...
-Because she was afraid...for you.  -Dad
我想清楚的知道她为什么会给你打电话
I wanna know exactly why the hell she would call you!
她看得出来你在逃避
She saw that you were slipping.
-你无法控制自己     -问题不是我能不能控制自己
-You were losing your grip.   -My grip is not the problem.
那正是现在发生这些事的原因
Which is exactly what's happening here.
算了吧 Jack
Jack! Come...
我认为你知道怎样让自己好点
I think I know a little something about being obsessive.
不  当一个酒鬼不是解决问题的办法
No,being a drunk is not obsessive.
放手吧 Jack
Let it go,Jack.
什么?
What?!
如果你是在和我说  那我听不见
If you're trying to talk to me,I can't hear you!
放手把 Jack
Let it go,Jack.
我知道你饿了
I know you're hungry.
我给你带了点吃的
I brought this for you.
现在我们这样
This is how it will work.
你坐在这里  背对着墙壁
You sit there,across from the door,back against the wall.
我把门打开留下盘子
I open the door and leave the tray.
我可以相信你吗?  Jack
Can I trust you to do that,Jack?
我不想要你的食物
I don't want your food.
这个三明治很可口...
It's a delicious sandwich...
我想你告诉对讲机那边的人  他可以放弃了
I want you to tell the guy who's talking to me through that intercom that he can give it up!
可能你现在真的很饿了
Maybe you're hungrier than you think.
那个对讲机已经坏了很多年了
That intercom hasn't worked in years.
那是什么?
What's that for?
那个按钮是用来干什么的?
The button-- what it's for?
是紧急时刻用的
It's for emergencies.
谁在监视我?
Who's watching me?
你能背靠着墙坐下吗? 这样我才能打开门
Are you going to sit against the wall so I can open the door?
这个煎饼刚刚才烤好
It's...just off the frying pan.
你自己吃吧
You can have it.
你是干什么的 Jack?
What do you do,Jack?
你的职业是什么?
What's your profession?
我是讨债的
I'm a repo man.
当人们不能按时付款时 我代替银行收回他们赊款的东西
You know,when people don't pay their bills,I go in for the bank,and I collect their possessions.
我是一个有人性的人 所以我很喜欢这个工作
I'm a people person,so I really love it.
你结婚了吗?
Are you married?
没有
No
从来都没有机会
I never saw the point.
你呢?
What about you?
除了做三明治你还有什么工作?
What's your job,besides making sandwiches?
这不是我做的
I didn't make it.
我只是把牙签插上去
I just put the toothpicks in.
当你们的飞机坠毁时 你们是从哪里起飞的?
When your plane crashed,where were you flying from?
悉尼
Sydney.
你在那里干什么?
What were you doing there?
我去把我爸爸带回家
I was bringing my father home.
-你走这么远的路只为了...    -因为他死了
-Why would you go all the way to Australia just to...  -because he was dead.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道
I'm sure you are.
谢谢
Thanks.
你可以相信我  Jack
You can trust me,Jack.
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
这里到底发生了什么事?
What the hell is going on here?
从这里到你们的营地需要多长时间?
How long would it take to get to your camp?
你现在肯跟我说话了吗  小子?
What,you're talking to me now,Chachi?
从他们抓到你的地方出发  需要多久 一天吗?  两天?
From where they got you,how long a walk was it--Day? Two days?
你们飞机上的那些人怎么样?
Hey,what are the people like--from your plane?
他们太可怕了
Oh,they're just awesome.
我们的伊拉克人拷打了你们最后一个 来参观我们营地的人
Last one of you boys came for a visit got tortured by our Iraqi.
他也拷打过我
He tortured me,too.
他自己再清楚不过了
Well,hell,he don't know any better.
*目标逃脱*
Subject escape.
你怎么出来的?
How'd you get out of there?
*目标逃脱*
Subject escape.
你往那边跑
You run that way.
-等一下      -你往那边跑
-Hold on...  -You run that way!
*目标逃脱*
Subject escape.
说吧
Say it!
说啊  Karl
Say it,Karl.
对不起
I'm...sorry.
我尝试逃跑却把你卷进来了
Sorry I involved you in my breakout attempt.
你刚来的时候我们给你的药有很强的副作用
The drugs we gave you when we brought you here have a fairly serious side effect--dehydration.
你的头会很痛
Your head is probably sore.
舌头变得干燥  并且如果你不尽快进食   就会产生幻觉
Your throat is raw,and if you don't eat
or drink something soon,you're going to start hallucinating.
那你是个医生了?
So you're a doctor,huh?
不
No.
我也是个讨债的
I'm a repo woman.
你不必被绑着
No strings attached.
你不需要回答问题
You don't have to answer any questions.
你什么都不用做  只要背靠墙坐好
You don't have to do anything but sit with your back up against the far wall.
我会打开门 放下盘子就走
Let me open that door,put the plate down and leave.
我知道如果你照做 就会好像你放弃了  输了
I know it feels like you're giving up,like you're
losing if you do anything that I ask you to.
但是你没有
But you're not.
你需要吃东西
You need to eat.
你说呢?
What do you say?
谢谢你  Jack
Thank you,Jack.
拔掉脑膜上的管子  进入观察阶段
Let's take out the epidural catheter and get him started on a P. C. A.
你确定他能自我恢复么?
You sure he's ready to self-administer his pain meds?
Shephard医生?
Dr. Shephard?
Jack?
把你的手机给我
Give me your cell phone.
-什么? 什...   -我现在就要看
-What?    -I wanna see it. Now.
看看你在哪儿  Jack
Look where you are,Jack.
拜托你四周看看
Just look around you,please.
把手机给我
Give me the phone!
这里不方便说这个
This is not the place for this.
你一定是Jack了
You must be Jack.
想坐下加入我们吗?
Why don't you,grab a chair and join us?
你...
You...
你认识我?
You know me?
是的
Yes.
你父亲经常和我们说起你
Your father's told us all about you.
是吗?  他说了我什么?
Yeah? What's he told you about me?
你和他们说了我什么  爸爸 那个你的...你的儿子总是失败者?
What'd you tell'em about me,dad-- that your--your son never really had it?
和他爸不一样
Not like the old man.
他不想成功  包括他的... 他的生活  他的工作  他的婚姻?
I didn't have the will to make it work-- my--my life,my job,my marriage?
关于我的婚姻你和他们说了什么  爸爸?
What'd you tell'em about my marriage,dad?!
你们知道他怎么安排的吗?
You know how he manages his marriage?
每晚吃饭钱喝一瓶苏格兰酒
A bottle of scotch every night before dinner.
你父亲已经50天没喝酒了
Your father has been sober 50 days now.
我们很为他骄傲
We're very proud of that.
喔  爸爸
Dad!
我想...是什么帮助了你?
I wonder what--what helped you turn that corner?
也许是...一个新的女朋友?
You think maybe it was--a new lady friend?
-你认为是这样... -我不会听你讲话了
-You think maybe that's what it was..  -I will not let you talk to me..
我不会让你和我妻子上床
I will not... sleep with my wife
Jack
Jack  我是你父亲
Jack,I'm your father.
Jack  求你了  放手吧
Jack,please,just let it go!
往哪儿出去?
Which way out?
别这么做  Jack
Don't do this,Jack.
不要
Don't.
-打开门       -不  我不能  我不能  Jack
-Open the door.  -No,I can't Jack.
-开了门我们就死了   -你骗我
-I do that, we die.   -You're lying to me.
我没有  没有
I'm not.
-打开门          -我发誓我不能
-Open the door!  -I swear I can't!
她说的是真的  Jack
She's telling the truth,Jack.
我对天发誓... 我会杀了她
I swear to god...I will kill her.
好吧
Okay.
反正你开了门她也会死的
Have her open the door,and she dies anyway.
我们都会死
We all do.
Jack
这里
Over here!
按钮
The button!
-什么    -黄色的按钮  按钮
-What?!  -The yellow button! The button!
*警告*
Warning.
成功了
Gotcha,doc!
*奖品*
Reward!
噢  拜托
Oh,come on.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
一直走
Keep movin'.
把手伸出来  我好把手铐拿下来
Stick your hands out through the bars.I'll take off your cuffs.
这手铐把你弄得够惨的  不是吗?
They scratched you up pretty bad,didn't they?
我过会给你带点消毒水
I'll bring you some antiseptic later.
给我来个长软椅怎么样?
How about you bring me an ottoman?
你忙的时候我能吹吹头发
While you're at it,I could use a blow-dry.
你弄到了个鱼形饼干
You got yourself a fish biscuit.
你怎么做到的?
How'd you do that?
我识破了你们的小发明  就是这样
I figured out your complicated gizmos,that's how.
上次那只熊只用了两个小时
Only took the bears two hours.
还有多少这样的?
How many of'em were there?
你没事吧  雀斑妹?
You okay,freckles?
没事
Yeah.
你呢?
You?
还不错
Just well.
本来我要求待在你那个笼子里的  但是..不管怎样
I requested that cage,but whatever.
衣服真漂亮
Nice dress.
他们逼我穿的
They made me wear it.
你饿么?
Are you hungry?
是个水族馆
It's an aquarium.
什么?
Excuse me?
这东西是干什么的...养鲨鱼?
This thing's for what...sharks?
也养海豚
Dolphins,too.
我们在水下  是吗?
We're underwater,aren't we?
是的
Yes.
这是他们站点的其中之一吗
Is this one of their...
那个达摩组织
stations-- the--the Dharma Initiative?
他们叫这个为九头蛇站
They called it the Hydra.
所以你们就是...
So you people are just...
他们留下的人?
whatever's leftover of them?
那是很久以前的事了
Well,that was a long time ago.
我们曾经是谁...
It doesn't matter...
已经不重要了
who we were.
重要的是我们现在是谁
It only matters who we are.
我们知道你的一切  Jack Shephard
We know exactly who you are,Jack Shephard.
你们一点都不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我们知道你是洛杉矶圣塞巴斯蒂安医院的 脊椎外科医生
We know that you're a spinal surgeon based out of St.Sebastian's hospital in Los Angeles.
我知道你去过哥伦比亚 并且你比别人早一年毕业
I know that you went to Columbia,and you graduated Med school a year faster than anyone else.
我知道你只结过一次婚  最后离了
I know that you were married,only once,and that you contested the divorce.
我知道你父亲在悉尼死了
I know your father died in Sydney.
我知道是因为我有一份验尸报告
I know this because I have a copy of his autopsy report.
你们...
How...
-你们怎么...     -我们弄到的
-How did you get...  -we got it.
那是什么?
What is that?
这些  Jack...
This,Jack...
是你的一生
is your life.
你们...
Do you...
这些只是关于我的   你们也有我家人和朋友的吗?
is it just about me,or is it about my family,too? My...My friends?
这儿基本上什么都有
It's pretty much about everything.
你知道我的...
Do you know about my...
我的...前妻么?
About my ex-wife?
Sarah
是的  Jack
Yes, Jack.
我们知道她的一切
We know all about her.
你想知道什么?
What would you like to find out?
Shephard  有人给你保释了
Shephard,someone posted your bail.
你怎么...
How'd you...
你爸爸告诉我你在这
Your dad told me you were here.
我给你叫了辆出租车
I called you a cab.
那么...
So...
再见了
good-bye.
Sarah
什么?
What?
就是他吗?
Is that him?
-是不是他有什么区别么?    -当然有区别
-What difference does it make?  -It just does.
-一切都不会改变了   -听着  我想知道
-It's not gonna change anything.   -Look,I wanna know!
我得知道他是谁
I need to know who he is.
他是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who he is.
重要的是 你不是那个人
It just matters who you're not.
Jack...
你父亲...
Your father...
他打给我电话...是为了帮你...
when he called me...to help you...
他当时很醉  我不明白他在说什么
he was so drunk,I could hardly understand him.
往好的方面想想吧
Look at the bright side.
现在你有事可做了
Now you have something to fix.
Jack?
你想知道什么?
What would you like to find out?
她...
Is she...
她现在快乐吗?
Is she happy?
是的  Jack
Yes,Jack.
她很快乐
She's very happy.
我想给你一些食物 但是这次我得确定你不会乱来
Now I'd like to bring you some food and water,but this time I need to know that you'll behave.
我能相信你吗  Jack?
Can I trust you,Jack?
拜托你靠墙站好
Put your back against the wall, please.
干得好  Juliet
Good work,Juliet.
谢谢  Ben
Thank you,Ben.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■